<pkmkdoc spec="1.12"><properties><title>Neurospaces Model Container</title><build>/Users/Abominous/src/Neurospaces Model Container.pkg</build><organization>neurospaces.developer</organization><userSees ui="easy"/><min-target os="3"/><domain system="true"/></properties><distribution><versions min-spec="1.000000"/><scripts></scripts></distribution><description>The Model Container is used as an abstraction layer on top of a simulator and deals with biological entities and end-user concepts instead of mathematical equations. It provides a solver independent internal storage format for models that allows user independent optimizations of the numerical core. 

By `containing' the biological model, the Model Container makes the implementation of the numerical core independent of software implementation. The Model Container API abstracts away all the mathematical and computational details of the simulator. 

Optimized to store large models in little memory--it stores neuronal models in a fraction of the memory that would be used by conventional simulators--and provides automatic partitioning of the model such that simulations can be run in parallel. From the modeler's perspective, the Model Container will be able to import and export NeuroML files to facilitate model exchange and ideas.

</description><contents><choice title="Package_Root" id="choice0" starts_selected="true" starts_enabled="true" starts_hidden="false"><pkgref id="neurospaces.model-container.pkg"/></choice></contents><resources bg-scale="none" bg-align="topleft"><locale lang="en"><resource relative="true" mod="true" type="license">../../OSX_BUILD/Resources/License.rtf</resource><resource relative="true" mod="true" type="welcome">../../OSX_BUILD/Resources/Welcome.rtf</resource><resource mime-type="text/rtf" kind="embedded" type="conclusion"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf949\cocoasubrtf540
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 LucidaGrande;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\ql\qnatural\pardirnatural

\f0\fs26 \cf0 The Neurospaces Model Container has been installed on your machine. Make sure that "/usr/local/bin" is in your path so you can call the model container tools from the command line. \
\
Also be sure to set one of the following environment variables to point to /usr/local/neurospaces/models/library :\
\
NEUROSPACES_NMC_PROJECT_MODELS, NEUROSPACES_NMC_SYSTEM_MODELS or NEUROSPACES_NMC_MODELS\
\
}]]></resource></locale></resources><requirements><requirement id="file" operator="eq" value="true"><file>/usr/bin/perl</file><message-title>Perl is not installed</message-title><message>Standard Perl for Mac OSX is not installed. Installed this from your Mac OSX installation disks since non-standard perl may cause errors. </message></requirement><requirement id="file" operator="eq" value="true"><file>/Library/Frameworks/Python.framework/Versions/Current/bin/python</file><message-title>Python is not installed</message-title><message>Python is not intalled on this system. Latest version can be downloaded from http://python.org/</message></requirement></requirements><flags/><item type="file">01package.xml</item><mod>properties.title</mod><mod>description</mod><mod>properties.anywhereDomain</mod><mod>properties.systemDomain</mod></pkmkdoc>